<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policies on Jose Vega for Congress 2024 | Power, Not Force.</title><link>https://votevega.nyc/policy/</link><description>Recent content in Policies on Jose Vega for Congress 2024 | Power, Not Force.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://votevega.nyc/policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a Space CCC: to Rebuild the Bronx and the U.S.</title><link>https://votevega.nyc/policy/space-ccc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://votevega.nyc/policy/space-ccc/</guid><description>&lt;p>The young people of the South Bronx today are faced with a miserable and hopeless future, ultimately the result of 50 years of benign neglect, planned shrinkage, and indifference of those who have shaped New York City&amp;rsquo;s financial and related policies. A report from New York State Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli, revealed in December 2022 that the Bronx had the highest poverty rate in the state at around 24%. The South Bronx itself has over 40% of its children living in poverty. The report further adds that among 16-to-24-year-olds in New York City, 18% of them are unemployed, with unemployment among young men hovering at 24%. This is merely a picture, not a whole overview of the problem, however, since the figures provided most likely underestimate the true unemployment, along with &amp;ldquo;underemployment&amp;rdquo; rates in the form of unproductive service and retail jobs.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Create A Truly Free Palestine Through The Oasis Plan</title><link>https://votevega.nyc/policy/oasis-plan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://votevega.nyc/policy/oasis-plan/</guid><description>&lt;p>On Sunday, February 25, U.S. Air Force member Aaron Bushnell set fire to himself in front of the Israeli embassy in Washington D.C., showcasing to the world the fate of over 30,000 Palestinians in the Gaza Strip. Over 90% of children under five now face disease, starvation, and rampant poverty, the result of a merciless, barbaric assault from Bibi Netanyahu&amp;rsquo;s genocidal regime in Israel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Bushnell live-streamed his self-immolation for millions to see. His action demonstrates, that the best young people in our nation, the most moral and patriotic, now believe there is no efficient recourse to averting the crime of genocide. There was no turning back from this act, no resistance from the pain that would follow. Bushnell&amp;rsquo;s act shows that we cannot ignore what is going on now in the Gaza Strip, in much the same way those who participated in the acts of the Nazi Regime, out of ignorance, fear, or malice, &amp;ldquo;knew, or should have known&amp;rdquo; the consequences of their actions. That same principle, set forth in the post-World War II trials of Nazi criminals at Nuremberg, applies to all of us now, where we see daily on our smart phones or computer screens the daily massacres now being committed in Gaza.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Approach to Economics</title><link>https://votevega.nyc/policy/economics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://votevega.nyc/policy/economics/</guid><description>&lt;p>My economic policy proposal at the federal level consists of what the economist Lyndon H. LaRouche in 2014 called his &amp;ldquo;Four Laws.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To begin to comprehend the scope and intention of this policy, it is necessary for you to understand the decades of political organizing through which these policies were formulated. But first, here are the laws:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The only location for the immediately necessary action which could prevent such an immediate genocide throughout the trans-Atlantic sector of the planet, requires the U.S. government&amp;rsquo;s now immediate decision to institute four specific cardinal measures — measures which must be fully consistent with the specific intent of the original U.S. Federal Constitution, as had been specified by U.S. Treasury Secretary Alexander Hamilton while in office.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to create "good" policy</title><link>https://votevega.nyc/policy/preamble/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://votevega.nyc/policy/preamble/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote class="blockquote text-center mb-5">
 &lt;p class="mb-3">"Increasingly, by choice or by accident, this is the role our nation has taken—the role of those who make peaceful revolution impossible by refusing to give up the privileges and the pleasures that come from the immense profits of overseas investment.&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;quot;mb-0&amp;quot;&amp;gt;I am convinced that if we are to get on the right side of the world revolution, we as a nation must undergo a radical revolution of values. We must rapidly begin the shift from a &amp;quot;thing-oriented&amp;quot; society to a &amp;quot;person-oriented&amp;quot; society. When machines and computers, profit motives and property rights are considered more important than people, the giant triplets of racism, materialism, and militarism are incapable of being conquered.&amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;footer class=&amp;quot;blockquote-footer mt-3&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., &amp;lt;cite title=&amp;quot;Beyond Vietnam: A Time to Break the Silence&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Beyond Vietnam: A Time to Break the Silence&amp;lt;/cite&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/footer&amp;gt;
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>To propose policy promoting the General Welfare in the United States today is to directly face decades and centuries of historical revisionism and ideological &amp;ldquo;disinformation campaigns&amp;rdquo; backed by state-sponsored terror and assassinations.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>